Finding Aid for the United Office and Professional Workers of America Records LSC.0963
UCLA Library Special Collections
United Office and Professional Workers of America records
circa 1929-1957
UCLA Library Special Collections
United Office and Professional Workers of America
LSC.0963
13.5 Linear Feet (27 boxes)
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Richard D. Lewis, 1967 & 1969.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942339043606533
Scope and Content
Collection consists of office files, miscellaneous publications, clippings, newspapers and periodicals, and a nearly complete run of the semi-weekly union paper, Union Voice, for 1950-54. Files include minutes of the general executive board and the administrative committee, financial records, and include materials on the CIO, contracts, government agencies, insurance, local unions, publicity, salaries, strikes, and the union constitution.
Labor unions -- United States -- Archives.; United Office and Professional Workers of America--Records and correspondence
- Office Files
  - CIO
    - National CIO - general., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - CIO Convention - correspondence., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - CIO Convention Proceedings - Portland, Oregon - November 1948. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - CIO - National (?) - UOPWA International., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - CIO - California State Convention., 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - National CIO - local statements., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - CIO - union policy in practice., 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - National CIO - clippings., 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - National CIO - UOPWA trials., 1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Anti-Discrimination Committee., n.d. (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Banking., 1944-1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Title companies., 1942-1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Commercial and Distributive
    - CIO Interference in UOPWA., 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - CIO Councils, etc., 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      Scope and Contents note
      Includes membership affiliation record (including estimated membership & PAC contributions), confidential.
    - National office - [UOPWA]., 1937-1947 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Contracts
    - Contracts., 1943-1951 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      General note
      Box 2 is no compromise size.
    - Contracts - Title Guarantee and Trust., 1943-1944 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Contract information., 1947-1951 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Contracts - Curtis Wright., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Contracts - Cutter Laboratories., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Contracts - Shell development., 1947 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Contracts - social services., 1946-1950 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Union contracts., 1948-1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Government Agencies
    - California - minimum wage., 1946 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - California - Tenney Committee., 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Statements & briefs - congressional committees., 1945 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - National Labor Relations Board., 1939-1946 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - National Wage Stabilization Board (empty)., n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - National War Labor Board - Little Steel Report - February 12, 1945. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - International Union - DPOWA
    - National War Labor Board., 1942-1946 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - U.S. Postal regulations (empty)., n.d. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - International Union - foreign policy., n.d. (post-World War II) (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - International Union - salary policy., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - International Union - Taft-Hartley., 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - International Union - Convention, 1950 - ... Resolutions. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - International Union - correspondence - general., 1944-1950 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - International Union - correspondence - Merrill [Lewis Merrill]., 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - International Union - correspondence - technical., 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - International union - DPOWA merger., 1950 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - International Union - FAECT merger., 1945 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Insurance
    - Local 178., 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Insurance., 1943-1950 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Insurance., 1946-1949 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Division conferences., 1937-1943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Insurance Division
    - 178 - Hancock., 1945-1950 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Policy and procedure., 1945-1949 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Unity Mutual., 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Golden State., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - American National - mailing lists (empty)., n.d. (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Social service., n.d. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Technical., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Box 4 is no compromise size.
    - Radio., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Hospital., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Banking., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Transportation plan - San Francisco., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - UOPWA - West Coast Region., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Southern California Council., 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Regional Executive Committee., 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - General Regional - (exc. insurance)., 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous., 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Prudential - Los Angeles Local 178 and West Coast releases., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Prudential., 1948-1949 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous., 1946-1949 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Local 178 Los Angeles - leaflets., 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - West Coast region., 1947-1949 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Organizing plans., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Accountant's Report for the year ending June 30, 1949. (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Reports to International., 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Publications
    - Champion (May 1938), Vocational Trends (June 1939). Union Research Facts and Figures, vol.1 no.1 (May 23, 1950)., 1938, 1939, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - UOPWA
    - Per capita reports, bulletins, press releases., 1940-1950 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Strike welfare guides., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Third Round Collective Bargaining Kit for CIO Unions in the Los Angeles Area, February 27, 1948. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Union Labor Committee - Unions expelled by CIO., 1950 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Resolutions, reports to members, press releases, Lewis Merrill resignation., 1946-1947 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Statement of the UOPWA... [on proposed amendments to the Fair Labor Standards Act]., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Classified., 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Lewis, Richard
    - Insurance., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Personal., 1945-1947 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Expense report forms (blank)., n.d. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Local Unions
    - West Coast region., 1944-1948 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Region - West Coast., 1946-1949 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Local 253 (including former Local 9)., 1946-1951 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Local 253 - retail credit., 1949 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Social Service - Los Angeles - (Local 95)., 1947-1950 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Duarte (including arbitration) - Local 95 - Los Angeles., 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Jewish Community Council (including Arbitration)., 1947-1950 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Local 34 - San Francisco, 1946-1947. (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Insurance industry., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Clippings - CIO and UOPWA activities., 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Statement re Harry Bridges, correspondence, ephemera] - labeled National Labor - Releases, 1946., 1946-1950 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Includes statement by Richard Lewis concerning indictment of Harry Bridges, correspondence between Richard Lewis and Bernard Lusher, and ephemera for related labor issues, 1946-1950.
    - News - UOPWA Press Service., 1941 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Follow-up., 1948-1951 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Prudential master plan., 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - International - printed leaflets and bulletins., 1948-1950 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Includes UOPWA poster re Prudential Insurance.
    - [file FE PRF868T254?] - No file present - Out marker dated 25 October 1982., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Prudential (empty)., n.d. (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Clippings - UOPWA locals., 1948-1953 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Clippings - general., 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - White Collar Conference, 1944. (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence from National on insurance., 1943-1953 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      Includes letters from Richard Lewis, Lewis Merrill.
    - Metropolitan - Organizing., 1945-1953 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      Penciled note on folder 1944-1945.
    - RD general correspondence with West Coast locals - officer list., 1944 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, financial analysis - DPOWA, [local and national reports...]., 1944-1951 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - International Union - correspondence., 1948-1951 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Local 75., 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Region - Social Service Division., 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      West Coast Regional Office - UOPWA.
    - [West Coast Regional Council]., 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      With correspondence and reports.
    - Banking., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - [Correspondence with local chapters and regional office, and related documentation]., 1946-1950 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Folder title Ins. Conf. Credentials has been crossed out.
    - Correspondence, bulletins - [local, regional, national]., 1948-1950 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Folder title CIO Councils has been crossed out.
    - Correspondence, confidential report, [UOPWA statement on Mundt-Ferguson bills...]., 1945-1949 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Folder title (Miscellaneous) - Filing.
      Includes California Intelligence Bureau confidential report - White Collar Workers Association, 1945, correspondence with William Piehl, Doris Walker, John Schuyten, and with regional and local offices.
    - West Coast region., 1948 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - BS and AU 12646 - Elections of officers., 1936 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - ACTU., n.d. (Box 8, Folder 2)
      How to de-control your union of communists, by Reverend Chalres Owen Rice.
    - Group insurance., 1940 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Prudential home office., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Personnel practices., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Folder title Personnel practises.
    - Photographs, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Photogaphs of picket lines at Cutter Laboratories, Radio Guild, Shell.
    - Publicity guide., 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Magazine articles re West Coast., n.d. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - National Social Services division., 1947-1950 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - National Labor Action Committee., 1944-1950 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Los Angeles Social Service., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Cedars of Lebanon., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Local 225 - Oakland - leaflets re Cutter, Shell., 1946-1948 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Local unions - 34 & 225 mainly., 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Prudential - San Francisco releases, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      Includes letter to Harry Bridges, 23 September 1948.
    - Metropolitan - releases., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - John Hancock negotiations - releases - bulletins. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Publicity
    - Miscellaneous., 1940-1946 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Includes correspondence, statistical reports, membership lists, publications, minutes.
    - Miscellaneous., 1940-1948 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      Includes correspondence, minutes, ephemera.
    - National Insurance Division, 1945-1944 - 3-2., 1944-1945 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Fraser correspondence - re secession of insurance agents from UOPWA, 1948. (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Includes carbon copies of letters as well as photostatic reproductions.
    - Other regions., 1948 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Press and government releases., 1944-1948 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Press release and charter - [UOPWA]., 1945 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - [Southern California Conference]., 1943-1948 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Local 19 New York - social service leaflets., 1945-1948 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Northern California Sub-regional Council., 1946-1949 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Financial., 1945-1948 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - [Social services locals and divisions]., 1942-1946 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Includes correspondence, minutes of meetings, issues of White Collars, The Office Worker, photograph of 1943 California CIO conference.
    - UOPWA - [national and local]., 1945-1950 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      Includes correspondence, administrative minutes, reports.
    - Local 9 Los Angeles - leaflets - later local 253., 1947-1953 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - [Publications on labor issues]., 1947-1949 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      [Includes:] Monthly Labor Review, vol.69 no.5 (November 1949), Industrial Bulletin, vol.28 no.6 (June 1949), and Survey of Personnel Practices in Los Angeles County, no.14 (August 1947) by Richard 0. Sensor & Mary Faith Martin.
    - Prices - clippings., 1951 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Cost of living (empty)., n.d. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Wages and personnel data., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - UOPWA - research [White collar workers salaries]., 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Clippings., 1944-1950 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Clippings and Discussion Material
    - [No further description available]., 1949 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Publicity
    - Classification and salary scales - [clerical positions]., 1948 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      Folder title is Filing - Newspapers.
    - CIO Convention - U.O.P.W.A. Statements., 1948-1949 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Publications., 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Folder title is Publications to file - news.
    - [Foreign white collar workers]., 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      The Clerk: the Federated Clerks' Union of Australia, 2 issues.
    - The Ledger - (BS & AU - AFL)., 1935-1936 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      Issues of The Ledger, publication of the Bookkeepers, Stenographers & Accountants' Union (Local 12646), including vol.1 no.1 (January 15, 1935).
  - Publications
    - Publications - Leaders Bulletin., 1947-1950 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      Issues of the UOPWA bulletin, including no.1 (November 7, 1947).
    - Organizers' Bulletin, UOPWA-1940. (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Issues of Organizers' Bulletin, including vol.1 no.1 (January 1940).
    - Organizers' Bulletin., 1941 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Publicity
    - Organizers' Bulletin., 1942-1944 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Salaries
    - White collar salary trends-1929-1933-1939, 1943-1945., 1929-1945 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Prepared by Salary Information and Research Department, UOPWA, October 1945.
    - [Wage proposals]., 1947 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Wage proposals for Poultry Producers of Central California (Petaluma branch) and Shell Development Corporation.
    - [Insurance plan for UOPWA employees]., 1945 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      Underwritten by John Hancock Mutual Life Insurance, Boston.
    - Salaries - clerical., 1943-1945 (?) (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Salary Bulletin - UOPWA., 1945 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      Issues of U.O.P.W.A. Bulletin, including vol.1 no.1 (February 1945), and no.3-5. Lacking no.2.
    - Salaries - social service., 1943-1950 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - White collar workers - middle class - New Masses articles., 1935-1936 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Strikes
    - Strike plans., 1947 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      re Shell Development Company.
    - Prudential - strike plans (empty)., n.d. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Strike plans - Federation., 1948 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      re Federation of Jewish Welfare Organizations.
    - Federation - injunction., 1950 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Federation - Report outline & special files., 1947-1952 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Local 95., 1950 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Federation - contract., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      re Federation of Jewish Welfare Organizations. Includes Memorandum of Understanding (January 20, 1950) and Extracts from Award.
    - Federation - Negotiations., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Federation - Correspondence with Managementt & Board., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Federation - International Union., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Federation - National Social Services Division., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Federation - UOPWA locals., 1950 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Federation - Loretta Levin itinerary]., 1950 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Folder title is Fed - Loretta Levin corresp. re Federation of Jewish Welfare Organizations.
    - Federation - membership lists., 1949 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Federation - General Schedules
    - 1950. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Strikes
    - Federation - financial statements., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Federation - leaflets to community., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Federation - leaflets to members no.95., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Leaflets to social work field., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Federation - press releases., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Federation - clippings., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - no.95 - Union Action Letter., 1948-1950 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Federation - picket schedules., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Newspaper clippings of Jewish Social Service Employees Strike Local - 95 - UOPWA - Master file., 1949-1950 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      Compiled by Mark Keats.
    - Federation - strike bulletins., 1950 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - General Executive Board - Minutes
    - General Executive Board - Minutes., 1942-1944 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - General Executive Board - Minutes., 1945-1946 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - General Executive Board Minutes., 1947 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - General Executive Board Minutes., 1948-1950 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Administrative Committee - Minutes
    - Administrative Committee Minutes., 1942-1943 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Administrative Committee Minutes., 1944 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Administrative Committee Minutes., 1945 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Committee Minutes., 1946 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Administrative Committee Minutes., 1947 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Committee Minutes., 1948-1949 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Administrative Committee Minutes., 1949-1950 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Constitution
    - Constitutional charter[?]., 1946-1948[?] (Box 17, Folder 1)
      Amendements to the Seventh Constitutional Convention, with copies of the UOPWA constitution, 1942, 1944, 1946, 1948.
    - Report of the UOPWA... 1937 to the Committee for Industrial Organization. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Report to the General Executive Board UOPWA., 1939 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Salaries - hospital - Franklin Hospital - wage brief., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Contracts
    - Agreement... between Bell Manufacturing... and Distributive, Processing and Office Workers., 1951 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Constitution
    - Convention call of the UOPWA., 1950 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      With bulletins.
  - Publications
    - Wage policy and collective bargaining for white collar & professional workers., 1947 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      Report by Lewis Alan Berne.
    - Unions for social workers?, 1940? (Box 17, Folder 8)
      Reprint of article by Ray Gordon, Trend, Fall 1940.
  - Research Material[?]
    - Wages, war and living costs... prepared by Research Department, American Newspaper Guild., 1941 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Publications
    - Publications for political action., 1948 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      Publications kit issued by CIO Political Action Committee.
    - C.I.O. publications - Citizen C.I.O. and The CIO: what it is and what it does., 1946? (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Financial Statements
    - Financial statements., 1947-1950 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Publications
    - Joe Worker and the story of labor, by Nat Schachner and Jack Alderman. (Box 17, Folder 13)
      History of labor presented in comic book format.
  - Financial Statements
    - Financial reports - [UOPWA]., 1940-1947 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      Includes payroll, organizing and defense funds, statement of assets and liabilities, analysis of local and national union income, and related material.
  - Publications
    - White collar day - mass meeting - Los Angeles - January 21, 1944. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - UOPWA - West Coast Region
    - Letterhead (blank)., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Finances., 1947-1949 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - West Coast Regional Council., 1946 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Bulletins, communications, memos, etc., 1946-1948 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - [Northern California Council]., 1946-1948 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - West Coast Regional - minutes., 1946-1948 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Southern California Sub-regional Council - Northwest., 1946-1948 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Union., 1949-1953 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      Includes bulletins, clipping (Daily News, 21 May 1951, p.5, Order union vote at film studio), letter to Richard Lewis? from Rose, 26 October 1949, re a 1937 strike.
    - Announcement 11 May 1953]. (Box 18, Folder 10)
      re DPOWA agreement with CIO.
    - UOPWA - [miscellaneous]., 1944, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      Statement re Fair Labor Standards Act, Statement of assets and liabilities (1950) and Resolutions (1950).
  - UOPWA - Financial
    - UOPWA financial secretary's manual., 1942-1945 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous
    - UOPWA Bulletin (March 1945) Labor Trends (10 April 1965) How to de-control your union..., 1945, 1965, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 13)
      Includes How to de-control your union of communists, by Reverend Charles Owen Rice.
  - Labor Issues - Clippings
    - Clippings file - UOPWA maintained], January 1946-March 1948., 1946-1948 and n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Includes: Labor Herald, Washington State C.I.O. News, San Francisco Chronicle, San Francisco Examiner, San Francisco Call Bulletin, San Francisco Register, San Francisco News, Daily Worker, Daily People's World, P.W., P.D.
  - Newspapers and Periodicals
    - Labor Herald, Southern California. August-December 1947., 12 items. (Box 19, Folder 2)
      1947: August 12, 19, 26; September 23; October 7, 21, 28; November 18; December 9, 16, 23, 30.
    - Labor Herald, Southern California. January-May 1948., 14 items. (Box 19, Folder 3)
      1948: January 6, 13, 20, 27; February 3, 10, 17, 24; March 9, 23; April 6, 13, 20; May 11.
    - Labor Herald, Southern California. July 26 and August 9, 1949., 2 items. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Labor Herald, Southern California. August 29, 1950., 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Labor Herald, Northern California. March-December 1947., 20 items. (Box 19, Folder 6)
      1947: March 7; April 22; June 10, 24; July 29; August 5, 26; September 2, 9, 16, 23; October 7, 21, 28; November 4; December 2, 9, 16, 23, 30.
    - Labor Herald, Northern California. January-December 1948., 22 items. (Box 19, Folder 7)
      1948: January 6, 13, 20, 27; February 3, 10, 17, 24; March 2, 9, 16, 30; April 6, 13, 27; May 4, 11, 18, 25; August 31; October 5; December 14.
    - Labor Herald, California. January-December 1948., 24 items. (Box 19, Folder 8)
      1948: January 20; March 30, 8, 15, 22, 29; July 6, 13, 20, 27; August 3, 10, 17, 24; September 7, 14, 21; October 5, 19, 26; November 23, 30; December 7, 21.
    - Labor Herald, California. January-November 1949., 19 items. (Box 19, Folder 9)
      1949: January 4, 11, 18, 25; February 1, 8, 15, 22; March 1, 8, 22; April 19; May 3, 17, 31; July 12, 26; August 23; November 29.
    - Labor Herald, California. January-March 1950., 2 items. (Box 19, Folder 10)
      January 31; March 28.
    - Labor Herald, California. January 2, 1951., 1 item. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Labor Herald, Warehouse Edition and unidentified. February 28, 1950 and n.d., 3 items. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Daily Worker. January-December 1947., 72 items. (Box 20, Folder 1)
      January 11, 13, 15, 25.
      February 11, 13, 24, 26, 27, 28.
      March 2, 3, 7, 13, 19, 20.